

ALVIN KARNADI

Makassar, Indonesia | 0895 801 552 360 | alvin.karnady@gmail.com August 2001 (22) | linkedin.com/in/alvin-karnady

PROFILE

A Fresh Graduate in computer science from Universitas Dipa Makassar, with skills in web and mobile development, as well as graphic design. With hands-on experience through campus and personal projects, as well as relevant internships. Fast learning and still continue learn new tech especially in software development and tools.

EDUCATION

Universitas Dipa Makassar | 2020 – March 2024

B.S. in Computer Science | GPA: 3.85

SMA Nasional Makassar | 2015 - 2018

Science Major

EXPERIENCE

Journey Event Planner & Orbit Event Organizer - Makassar, Indonesia

Event Coordinator (2018 - Present)

- Coordinated events from start to finish, ensuring smooth operation.
- Built strong relationships with clients to meet their event needs.
- Managed vendors to ensure every aspect of the event worked perfectly.

PT. Telkom Regional VII - Makassar, Indonesia

Regional Operation Center Intern (Aug 2023 - Sep 2023)

- Developed fullstack web application for employee leave requests using Laravel Framework.
- Updated and maintained accurate client data.

PT. Medianet Sukses Abadi – Makassar, Indonesia

IT Support Technician (Nov 2018 - Nov 2022)

- Installed and maintained clients' computer systems, software, and networks.
- Installed and maintained clients' CCTV.

ORGANIZATIONAL EXPERIENCE

Naga Langit Indonesia - Makassar, Indonesia

Atlet (2010 - 2024)

- Following a regular exercise routine
- Participating in competitions at the city, provincial, national, and international levels
- Maintaining a healthy lifestyle.

SKILLS & TOOLS

- Database (MySQL, Laragon)
- Languange (Php, Html, css, Javascript, Python)
- Framework (Laravel, Flutter, NextJs, Bootstrap)
- Tools (VSCode, GitHub), (CorelDraw, Photoshop)

SOFT SKILLS

- Ms. Office (Word, Excel, Power Point)
- Prompt Al
- Detail orientation
- Adaptability
- Communication
- Problem solving

OTHERS

Certificate : BNSP Junior Graphic Design, BNSP Junior Network Administrator,
BNSP Creating 3D Animation Movement.

Courses & Training
: Jago Flutter FIC Batch 16 Fullstack Flutter Laravel – Membangun
Aplikasi Absensi dengan Face Recognition & GPS Location,

Coding Studio Mahir Membuat Website dengan Laravel 9,

Digitalent Kominfo VSGA Junior Graphic Design,

Digitalent After Class: Goes to Makassar,

Digitalent Kominfo VSGA Junior Network Administrator,

BDI Denpasar 3D Animation Movement.